Guide to the Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York Records and Photographs WAG.009
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series III: Records of the Professional Staff Congress, 1926-2009
  - Subseries III:B: Officers and Staff Files, 1926-2009
    - Sub Subseries III:B:3: Irwin Polishook Files, 1969-2000
      - Class Size, undated (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - Coalition Agreement, 1978, 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - Coalition Agreement, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - Coalition of Municipal Labor Unions, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - College Laboratory Technicians (CLT) Chapter, 1976-1984 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - CLT Chapter, 1994-1997 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - College of Staten Island, 1976-1984 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - College of Staten Island, 1991-1994 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Commission on Academic Personnel Practice, undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Commission on Academic Personnel Practice, 1969-1973 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Commission on Academic Personnel Practice (I), 1974 (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Commission on Academic Personnel Practice (II), 1974 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Commission on Academic Personnel Practice (III), 1974 (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - Commission on Academic Personnel Practice, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Commission on Academic Personnel Practice: Tenure, 1971-1974 (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - Committee for Public Higher Education, 1978-1981 (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - Committee for Public Higher Education, 1984-1998 (Box 39, Folder 14)
      - Committee on Higher Education, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - Committees (PSC), 1974 (Box 39, Folder 16)
      - Communist Party (Teachers Club), undated (Box 39, Folder 17)
      - Community Colleges, 1978-1983 (Box 39, Folder 18)
      - Community Colleges, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 19)
      - Community Colleges, 1997-1999 (Box 39, Folder 20)
      - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Program, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 21)
      - Consortium for Worker Education, 1993-1997 (Box 39, Folder 22)
      - Constitution (PSC), 1972-1978 (Box 39, Folder 23)
      - Cook, Kenneth, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 39, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1998-2000 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Council for Higher Education Accreditation, undated, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Council of Municipal Retiree Organizations of NYC (COMRO), 1981, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Council on Foreign Language Study, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Credit Union, 1978-1984 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Cuban Studies, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - CUNYCard, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Cuomo, Mario, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Deferral of Pay (Fiscal Crisis), 1976- 1984 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Delegate Assembly, 1973, 1976-1979 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Delegate Assembly, 1980-1984 (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Delegate Assembly, 1991-2000 (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - DeMelas, Anthony, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Discrimination against Jews, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Distance Education, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 15)
      - Distinguished Professors, 1979-1983 (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - Doctoral Equivalency, undated, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - Doctoral Students' Council, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - Dowling College, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - Dues, 1973-1983 (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - Early Retirement, 1978-1984, 1992-1996 (Box 41, Folder 21)
      - Education Commission of the States, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 22)
      - Educational Opportunity Centers, 1978-1980 (Box 41, Folder 23)
      - Educational Technology Office, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 24)
      - Engineering Faculty, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 25)
      - Elections (PSC) (I), 1973 (Box 41, Folder 26)
      - Elections (PSC) (II), 1973 (Box 41, Folder 27)
      - Elections (PSC), undated (Box 41, Folder 28)
      - Elections (PSC), 1976 (Box 41, Folder 29)
      - Elections (PSC), 1978-1982 (Box 41, Folder 30)
      - Elections (PSC), 1997-1999 (Box 41, Folder 31)
      - Empire State College, 1977, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 32)
      - Enrollment, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 33)
      - Evaluation, 1975-1984 (Box 41, Folder 34)
      - Evaluation of the Chancellor, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 35)
      - Executive Council, 1977-1979 (Box 41, Folder 36)
      - Executive Council, 1980-1984 (Box 41, Folder 37)
      - Executive Council, 1991-2000 (Box 41, Folder 38)
      - Facilities, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 39)
      - Fact-Finder's Report, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 40)
      - Faculty Development, 1980-1982 (Box 41, Folder 41)
      - Faculty Referral Service, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 42)
      - Faculty Senate, 1970-1975 (Box 41, Folder 43)
      - Faculty Senate, 1976-1982 (Box 41, Folder 44)
      - Faculty Senate, 1995-1997 (Box 41, Folder 45)
      - Faculty Status, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Faculty Transfers, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Faculty Workload, 1976-1983, 1997-1999 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Finances, 1973, 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Fiscal Problems (NYC), 1989-1990 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Foreign Language Instruction, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Fowler, George H. (BMCC), 1977 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Friends of CUNY, 1979-1984, 1999-2000 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Furlough, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Gay Academic Union, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Gay Teachers Association, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Guiliani, Rudolph, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Goldstein Report, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - Governance, 1969-1974 (Box 42, Folder 14)
      - Governance, 1978-1984 (Box 42, Folder 15)
      - Governance, 1986-1989 (Box 42, Folder 16)
      - Governor's Hearings, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 17)
      - Graduate Center Chapter, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 18)
      - Graduate Center for Worker Education, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 19)
      - Graduation Rates, undated (Box 42, Folder 20)
      - Grievance Policy Committee, 1973-1977, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 21)
      - Grievances, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 22)
      - Health and Safety, 1980-1983, 1994-1997 (Box 42, Folder 23)
      - Higher Education Officers (HEO's) Cross Campus Chapter, 1977-1997 (Box 42, Folder 24)
      - History Department, CCNY (Koster Committee, Etc.), 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 25)
      - History: CUNY, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 26)
      - History Department, CUNY: External Review, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 27)
      - Home Study (English Language), 1979-1981 (Box 42, Folder 28)
      - Hostos Community College, 1974-1983 (Box 42, Folder 29)
      - Hostos Community College, 1991-1998 (Box 42, Folder 30)
      - Howe Report, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 31)
      - Hunter College, 1976-1984 (Box 42, Folder 32)
      - Hunter College, 1990-1996 (Box 42, Folder 33)
      - Immigration Control and Financial Responsibility Act of 1996 (Box 42, Folder 34)
      - Incentives to Forego Tenure, 1999-2000 (Box 42, Folder 35)
      - Intra-University Mobility, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 36)
      - Italian-American Affairs, 1973, 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 37)
      - Italian-American Affairs, 1992-1996 (Box 42, Folder 38)
      - Jeffries, Professor Leonard, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 39)
      - Jewish Faculty Association, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 40)
      - Jewish Labor Committee, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 41)
      - Jobs and the University Conference, 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 42)
      - John Jay College, 1977-1984, 1991-1996 (Box 42, Folder 43)
      - Kibbee, Robert, 1978-1983 (Box 42, Folder 44)
      - Kingsborough Community College, 1974-1983 (Box 42, Folder 45)
      - Kingsborough Community College, 1992-1999 (Box 42, Folder 46)
      - Koch, Ed, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 47)
      - Kugler, Israel, 1973-1980, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 48)
      - Labor Education, 1976-1981 (Box 42, Folder 49)
      - Labor Studies, 1977-1979 (Box 42, Folder 50)
      - LaGuardia Community College, 1981-1992, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 51)
      - Language Immersion Program, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 52)
      - Legislative, 1976-1979 (Box 42, Folder 53)
      - Legislative, 1980-1984 (Box 42, Folder 54)
      - Legislative, 1991-1995 (Box 42, Folder 55)
      - Legislative Committee, undated (Box 42, Folder 56)
      - Lehman College, 1971-1974 (Box 42, Folder 57)
      - Lehman College, 1976-1983 (Box 42, Folder 58)
      - Lehman College, 1995-1998 (Box 42, Folder 59)
      - Librarians, 1975-1983, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Lobbying (PSC), 1978-1979, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Long Island University, 1980-1983 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Lutzker, Michael, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Mandatory Retirement, 1977-1985 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Mandatory Retirement, 1986-1992 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Marino, Ronald, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Master Plan, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Mayoral Campaign Issues, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - McCall, Carl, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - Medgar Evers College, 1978-1994 (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - Melani Case, 1978, 1982-1983 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - Membership Campaign, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Membership Services, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - Merger of CUNY and SUNY (proposed), 1992 (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - Mobilization Committee, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - Mobilization Coordinating Committee, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 17)
      - Multiple Positions, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 18)
      - Municipal Labor Committee, 1978-1984 (Box 43, Folder 19)
      - Municipal Labor Committee, 1989-1999 (Box 43, Folder 20)
      - Nassau Community College, 1977-1982 (Box 43, Folder 21)
      - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, 1977-1980, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 22)
      - National Education Association (NEA), 1976 (Box 43, Folder 23)
      - NEA, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 24)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 25)
      - New Caucus, 1996-1998 (Box 43, Folder 26)
      - New York City Central Labor Council, 1973-1979, 1990-1996 (Box 43, Folder 27)
      - New York City Community College, 1975-1980 (Box 43, Folder 28)
      - New York City Technical College, 1982-1983, 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 29)
      - New York-New Jersey Faculty Action, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 30)
      - New York State Association of Black and Puerto Rican Legislators, 1995-1997 (Box 43, Folder 31)
      - New York State United Teachers (NYSUT), undated (Box 43, Folder 32)
      - NYSUT, 1979-1984 (Box 43, Folder 33)
      - NYSUT, 1991-1995 (Box 43, Folder 34)
      - NYSUT, 1996-2000 (Box 43, Folder 35)
      - New York University, 1977, 1980-1983 (Box 43, Folder 36)
      - Newt Davidson, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 37)
      - Nielson, Robert, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 38)
      - Nielson-Polishook Articles, 1979-1990 (Box 43, Folder 39)
      - Non-continuing employment, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 40)
      - Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU), Local 153, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 41)
      - Office Space, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 42)
      - Officers' Meeting, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 43)
      - Open Admissions, 1972-1977 (Box 43, Folder 44)
      - Open Admissions, 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 45)
      - Optional Retirement Program: Task Force, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Optional Retirement Program: Task Force (I), 1992 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Optional Retirement Program: Task Force (II), 1992 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Optional Retirement Program: Task Force (III), 1992 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Optional Retirement Program: Task Force, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Pataki, George, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Peer Judgement, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Pell Grants, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Pennsylvania Federation of Teachers, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Pension Plan, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Pensions, 1976-1983, 1992-1998 (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Personnel Practices, undated (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Polishook, Amoda, et. al. vs. City University of New York, 1996-1997 (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - Polishook, Lewis, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - Political Activity, 1976-1984 (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - Political Activity, 1991-1998 (Box 44, Folder 16)
      - Private Higher Education, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 17)
      - Productivity, undated (Box 44, Folder 18)
      - Professional Staff Congress vs. Board of Higher Education (Supreme Court of New York), 1975 (Box 44, Folder 19)
      - Professional Staff Union, 1973-1975 (Box 44, Folder 20)
      - Professional Staff Union, undated (Box 44, Folder 21)
      - Project on Faculty Appointments, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 22)
      - Public Programs (PSC), 1997 (Box 44, Folder 23)
      - Public Relations (PSC), 1977-1979 (Box 44, Folder 24)
      - Publicity, undated, 1976-1995 (Box 44, Folder 25)
      - Queens College, 1976-1984, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 26)
      - Queens College: Worker Education Program, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 27)
      - Queensborough Community College, undated, 1969-1982 (Box 44, Folder 28)
      - Queensborough Community College, 1991-1992 (Box 44, Folder 29)
      - Regents, 1978-1979 (Box 44, Folder 30)
      - Regents Plan, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 31)
      - Remediation, undated, 1976-1978 (Box 44, Folder 32)
      - Remediation, 1996-2000 (Box 44, Folder 33)
      - Reorganization (CUNY), 1993 (Box 44, Folder 34)
      - Research Awards, 1980-1981, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 35)
      - Research Foundation, 1977-1984 (Box 44, Folder 36)
      - Research Foundation, 1996-1997 (Box 44, Folder 37)
      - Residency, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 38)
      - Restructuring, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 39)
      - Retirees Chapter, 1982-1984, 1993-1998 (Box 44, Folder 40)
      - Retirement, 1982, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 41)
      - Retrenchment, 1975-1976 (Box 44, Folder 42)
      - Retrenchment, 1977-1984 (Box 44, Folder 43)
      - Retrenchment, 1992-1996 (Box 44, Folder 44)
      - Riley Commission, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 45)
      - Richmond College, 1974-1975 (Box 44, Folder 46)
      - Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, 1981-1983, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 47)
      - Rohatyn, Felix, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 48)
      - Sabbaticals, 1979-1981 (Box 44, Folder 49)
      - St. Croix Federation of Teachers, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 50)
      - Salaries, 1976-1983, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 51)
      - Schmidt Task Force, undated (Box 44, Folder 52)
      - Scholarship Funds (PSC), 1979 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Security (CUNY), 1995-1996 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Senate Higher Education Committee, 1980, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Sex Discrimination, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Sexual Harassment, 1995-1996 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Sexual Orientation, undated (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Shanker, Albert, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Siegel, Mark, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Simmons, Curtis, 1995-1998 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - Southern University (Baton Rouge, LA), 1972 (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - Speeches, undated, 1976-1977 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - Starling, Marion, undated, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - State Investment in Higher Education (PSC Report), 1978 (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - Student Achievement, 1991-1993 (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - Student Achievement (I), 1994 (Box 45, Folder 15)
      - Student Achievement (II), 1994 (Box 45, Folder 16)
      - Student Achievement, 1995-1996 (Box 45, Folder 17)
      - Student Demonstrations, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 18)
      - Student Disciplinary Procedures, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 19)
      - Student Retention Project, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 20)
      - Student Senate, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 21)
      - Student Services, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 22)
      - Students' Role in Bargaining, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 23)
      - Substitutes, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 24)
      - Summer Schedule, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 25)
      - Tenure, undated (Box 45, Folder 26)
      - Tenure, 1972-1980 (Box 45, Folder 27)
      - Tenure, 1982-1984 (Box 45, Folder 28)
      - Tenure, 1992-1995 (Box 45, Folder 29)
      - Tenure, 1996-1999 (Box 45, Folder 30)
      - Tenure Quotas, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 31)
      - Tenure Quotas, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 32)
      - Testimony, 1976-1983 (Box 45, Folder 33)
      - Testimony, 1984-1995 (Box 45, Folder 34)
      - Testing, 1977-1982 (Box 45, Folder 35)
      - Trustees (CUNY), 1994-1998 (Box 45, Folder 36)
      - TIAA-CREF, 1977, 1991-1994 (Box 45, Folder 37)
      - Treasurer (PSC), 1979 (Box 45, Folder 38)
      - Tuition, 1977-1983, 1991-1992 (Box 45, Folder 39)
      - Tuition Assistance Program (TAP), 1976-1981 (Box 45, Folder 40)
      - Tuition Tax Credit, 1978, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 41)
      - Tuition Waiver Plan, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 42)
      - Union Caucus, undated, 1974-1994 (Box 45, Folder 43)
      - United Nations, undated (Box 45, Folder 44)
      - United Professors of California, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 45)
      - United University Professions (UUP), undated, 1977-1982, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 46)
      - Unity Caucus, 1975-1984, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 47)
      - Van Arsdale, Harry, 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 48)
      - Voorhees Chapter, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 49)
      - Wagner College Strike, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 50)
      - Web-site (PSC), 1999 (Box 45, Folder 51)
      - Welfare Fund, 1977-1980 (Box 45, Folder 52)
      - Welfare Fund, 1981-1988 (Box 45, Folder 53)
      - Welfare Fund, 1991-1995 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Welfare Fund, 1996-2000 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Welfare Fund: Petition to, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Welfare Fund Trustees, 1976-1982 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Welfare Fund Trustees, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Welfare Fund Trustees: Report to, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Wessell Commission, 1976-1977 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Westchester Community College, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Women's Resource Center (Queensboro Community College), undated (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Women's Studies, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Workfare, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - Workload, 1975-1977 (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - Workload: Consent Award, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 13)
      - Workload Grievances: Arbitration, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 14)
      - Yeshiva University, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 15)
      - York College, undated, 1974-1982 (Box 46, Folder 16)
      - York College, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 17)
      - York College, 1994-1995 (Box 46, Folder 18)
      - Zeller, Belle, 1974-1984 (Box 46, Folder 19)
      - Zeller, Belle: Scholarship, 1980-1984, 1992-1998 (Box 46, Folder 20)
      - Zeller, Belle: Scholarship Trust Fund, 1978-1982 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Sub Subseries III:B:4: Irwin Yellowitz Files, 1977-2009
      - American Association of University Professors Elections, 1983-1997 (Box 46, Folder 21a)
      - American Association of University Professors-National Education Association Joint Projects, 1985-1992 (Box 46, Folder 22)
      - American Federation of Teachers (AFT)/ COPE, 1985-1992 (Box 46, Folder 23)
      - Awards Dinners, undated (Box 46, Folder 24)
      - Bargaining, 1984-1987 (Box 46, Folder 25)
      - Baruch College, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 25a)
      - Borough of Manhattan Community College, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 25b)
      - Brooklyn College, 1993-1996 (Box 46, Folder 25c)
      - Center for Constitutional Rights Lawsuit, 1991-1993 (Box 46, Folder 26)
      - Center for Labor-Management Policy, 1988-1993 (Box 46, Folder 27)
      - CUNY: Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 46, Folder 28)
      - CUNY: Budget (Student Demonstrations, etc.), 1988 (Box 46, Folder 29)
      - CUNY: Budget (Student Demonstrations, etc.), 1989 (Box 46, Folder 30)
      - Credit Union, 1986-1990 (Box 46, Folder 31)
      - Early Retirement, 1990, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 32)
      - Eisenberg v. Polishook et al, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 33)
      - Elections (1986): Lehman College (Box 46A, Folder 1)
      - Elections (1987): Baruch College (Box 46A, Folder 2)
      - Elections (1987):Hostos Community College (Box 46A, Folder 3)
      - Elections (1987): Kingsborough Community College (Box 46A, Folder 4)
      - Elections (1989): Kingsborough Community College -- Aranoff Slate (Box 46A, Folder 5)
      - Elections (1989): Kingsborough Community College -- Eisenberg Slate (Box 46A, Folder 6)
      - Elections (1990): City College (Box 46A, Folder 7)
      - Elections (1991): City University Union Caucus (CUUC) (Box 46A, Folder 8)
      - Elections (1991): Opposition Candidates (Box 46A, Folder 9)
      - Elections (1991): Results (Box 46A, Folder 10)
      - Elections (1992): Kingsborough Community College April Election -- Chapey/Eisenberg Slate (Box 46A, Folder 11)
      - Elections (1992): Kingsborough Community College April Election -- Keller Slate (Box 46A, Folder 12)
      - Elections (1992): Kingsborough Community College Court Case (Box 46A, Folder 13)
      - Elections (1992): Kingsborough Community College December Election -- Chapey/Eisenberg Slate (Box 46A, Folder 14)
      - Elections (1992): Kingsborough Community College December Election -- Keller Slate (Box 46A, Folder 15)
      - Elections (1993): Brooklyn College (Box 46A, Folder 16)
      - Elections (1993): City College (Box 46A, Folder 17)
      - Elections (1994): General (Box 46A, Folder 18)
      - Elections (1994): Kingsborough Community College (Box 46A, Folder 19)
      - Elections (1995): Borough of Manhattan Community College (Box 46A, Folder 20)
      - Elections (1996): Baruch College (Box 46A, Folder 21)
      - Elections (1996): City College (Box 46A, Folder 22)
      - Elections (1996): Queens College (Box 46A, Folder 23)
      - Elections (1997): City University Unity Caucus (CUUC) (Box 46A, Folder 24)
      - Elections (1997): City University Unity Caucus (CUUC) Campus Materials (Box 46A, Folder 25)
      - Elections (1997): City University Unity Caucus (CUUC) Clarion Material (Box 46A, Folder 26)
      - Elections (1997): New Caucus (Box 46A, Folder 27)
      - Elections (1997): Procedural Issues (Box 46A, Folder 28)
      - Elections (1997): Results (Box 46A, Folder 29)
      - Elections (1999): Brooklyn College, La Guardia Community College, and Hunter College (Box 46A, Folder 30)
      - Elections (2000): City University Unity Caucus (CUUC) (Box 46A, Folder 31)
      - Elections (2000): General (Box 46A, Folder 32)
      - Elections (2000): New Caucus (Box 46A, Folder 33)
      - Elections: Borough of Manhattan Community College Chair Mayer Rossabi, 1988-1991 (Box 46A, Folder 34)
      - Elections: City University Unity Caucus (CUUC), 1996-1999 (Box 46A, Folder 35)
      - Elections: City University Unity Caucus (CUUC), 2001 (Box 46A, Folder 36)
      - Elections: General, 1985-1988 (Box 46A, Folder 37)
      - Elections: General, 2002-2009 (Box 46A, Folder 38)
      - Elections: HEO Chapter, 1989-1992 (Box 46A, Folder 39)
      - Elections: Kingsborough Community College, 1995-1996 (Box 46A, Folder 40)
      - Elections: La Guardia Community College, 1990-1996 (Box 46A, Folder 41)
      - Elections: New Caucus and Other Groups, 1997-1999 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Kingsborough Community College, 1986-1988 (Box 47, Folder 1a)
      - Kingsborough Community College, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Kingsborough Community College, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 2a)
      - Legislative, 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 3)